...we imply that we will be
the crushers of Wesley.
I'm sorry, but the Wesley Crushers...
...sounds like people
who like Wesley Crusher.
No, again,
it's not the Wesley Crushers.
It's the Wesley "Crushers."
No, if you want it to mean
you're crushing Wesley...
...it'd be the "Wesley" Crushers.
(Sheldon:)Do you people even hear yourselves?
It's not the Wesley Crushers.
It's not the "Wesley" Crushers,
it's Wesley "Crushers."
(Wil:)Hey, look.
They named their team after me.
No, it's not-- Never mind.
(Stuart:)So we're all clear on the bet
and the stakes?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes.
(Sheldon:)The losers will be publicly humiliated
in a fashion to be chosen by the victor.
(Sheldon:)FYI, I plan on having you
publish a scientific paper...
(Sheldon:)...expounding the discredited
Belakovsky hypotheses.
(Stuart:)Ouch again.